Guide to the Rice University Student Association records, 1918-2013 UA 252
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series XV: Addenda 2016
  - Sub-Series VII: Organizations
    - Rice Investment Group (R.I.G.), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Iota Sigma Pi, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Rice Iranian Society, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - The Islamic Society at Rice (ISR), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Israeli-Palestinian Dialogue Group, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Japanese Association of Students and Scholars, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Rice Jazz Society, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Rice University Jewish Community Relations Council, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Jude & Jiu-Jitsu, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - The Rice Juggling Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Junior Achievement, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - Kairos Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - Karaoke and DDR Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - Kinesiology Majors, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - Korean International Student Association, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - Korean Student Association of Rice University, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - The Rice University Kung Fu Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 52)
    - Rice Lacrosse Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 53)
    - Rice University Latin American L****** Association (RULALA), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 54)
    - Latin American Student Association, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 55)
    - Latter-Day Saint Student Association, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 56)
    - Rice Lead... Or Leave, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 57)
    - Leaders for Change, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 58)
    - Rice Lebanese Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 59)
    - College Libertarians of Rice University, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 60)
    - Rice Light Opera Society, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 61)
    - Lights in Action, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 62)
    - Rice Linguistics Society, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 63)
    - Rice Linux Users Group, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 64)
    - The Lipstick Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 65)
    - Lone Star Society, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 66)
    - The Rice Low Keys, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 67)
    - Lutheran Student Movement at Rice University, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 68)
    - Macrocosm, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 69)
    - Management Consulting Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 70)
    - Maranatha Campus Ministry, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 71)
    - Marcus Aurelius Latin & English Society, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 72)
    - Rice University Math Clubs, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 73)
    - Melodious Voices of Praise Gospel Choir (MVP), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 74)
    - The Rice University Society of Mexican American Engineers & Scientists/Society of Hispanic Professional Engineers (MAES/SHPE), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 75)
    - Rice Association of Mexican-American Students, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 76)
    - Men's Club Basketball, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 77)
    - Rice U Men's Soccer Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 78)
    - Men's Volleyball Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 79)
    - Mentis: The Rice University Journal of Brain Studies, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 80)
    - Mind Over Madness: The Rice Atheist Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 81)
    - Rice University Minority Association of Pre-Health Students (Rice-MAPS), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 82)
    - The Rice Minority Student Advisory Group, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 83)
    - The MTech Club at Rice, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 84)
    - Music Without Borders, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 85)
    - Muslim Student Association, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 86)
    - The Rice University Mystic Inspirations (RUMI) Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 87)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored Peoples Rice University Chapter (NAACP), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 88)
    - The National Society of Black Engineers, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 89)
    - The National Society of Collegiate Scholars, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 90)
    - Native American Student Association, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 91)
    - The Navigators, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 92)
    - Net Impact Rice University Chapter, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 93)
    - The Rice University Neuroscience Society, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 94)
    - New Life, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 95)
    - New Party, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 96)
    - Rice University Nippon Cultural Society, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 97)
    - The Association of Non-Traditional Students, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 98)
    - Rice University NSSLHA Chapter, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 99)
    - Rice Objectivism Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 100)
    - Rice Objectivist Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 101)
    - Oikumenei, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 102)
    - Optical Society of America, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 103)
    - The Oriental Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 104)
    - Orthodox Christian Fellowship, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 105)
    - Outdoors Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 106)
    - The Rice Outreach Program, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 107)
    - Outreach Tutoring, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 108)
    - The Owen Wister Library Society, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 109)
    - Owlchemy, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 110)
    - The Oxfam Group, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 111)
    - Rice Paintball Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 112)
    - Partnership for the Advanced & Immersion of Refugees (PAIR), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 113)
    - The Rice Peace Forum, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 114)
    - Peer Health Information and Support (PHIS) Service, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 115)
    - The Rice Philharmonics, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 116)
    - Rice University's Philosophy Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 117)
    - Rice Photonic Owls SPIE Student Chapter, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 118)
    - Ping-Pong Players Anonymous, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 119)
    - Rice Poets Society, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 120)
    - The Policy Studies Society, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 121)
    - Rice Powerlifting Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 122)
    - Practical Self Defense Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 123)
    - The Pre-Law Organization at Rice University, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 124)
    - The Rice Pre-Medical Society, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 125)
    - Rice Pre-Veterinary Club (RPVC), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 126)
    - Rice Pro-life Movement, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 127)
    - The Rice Chapter of the Project Management Institute, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 128)
    - Psi Chi, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 129)
    - The PSI Study Group, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 130)
    - Rice Psychology Association, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 131)
    - Puzzle Masters Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 132)
    - quirkHouston, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 133)
    - Rice University Quiz Bowl, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 134)
    - Rice Racquetball Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 135)
    - The Rainbow Rockers Square Dancing Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 136)
    - The Rally Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 137)
    - Rambunctious Eccentrics Disrespectfully Reviewing Underrated Movies (Red Rum), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 138)
    - The Rice Rappelling Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 139)
    - Rice R/C Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 140)
    - Rice Real Estate Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 141)
    - Rice Recreational Runners, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 142)
    - Religion of the Month Club (RMC), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 143)
    - Reformed University Fellowship at Rice University, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 144)
    - Rice Renegade Ninja Society, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 145)
    - RHAPSODY, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 146)
    - Rice Cakes, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 147)
    - Rice Extreme Dancers (R.E.D.), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 148)
    - Rice for Choice, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 149)
    - Rice for Freedom, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 150)
    - Rice for Legislation, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 151)
    - Rice for Peace, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 152)
    - Rice for Thought, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 153)
    - Rice for UNICEF, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 154)
    - Rice Program Council, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 155)
    - Rice Road Runners, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 156)
    - Rice Students for Organ Donation, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 157)
    - Rice University Court, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 158)
    - The Roosevelt Institution, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 159)
    - The Rice Rostrum, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 160)
    - The Rotaract Club of Rice University, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 161)
    - Rice Rowing Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 162)
    - Rice University Rugby Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 163)
    - Club for Russian Speakers at Rice, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 164)
    - Ruz, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 165)
    - Rice University S.A.A.C., n.d. (Box 26, Folder 166)
    - Rice Salseros, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 167)
    - Rice Science Fiction, Fantasy, and Anime Society, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 168)
    - Science Olympiad, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 169)
    - Rice Scientists and Engineers for America (RICE-SEA), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 170)
    - Rice Scrabble Society, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 171)
    - Secular Students of Rice, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 172)
    - S.E.E.K., n.d. (Box 26, Folder 173)
    - Senior Committee, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 174)
    - Sewa International at Rice, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 175)
    - Shepherd School Outreach Team, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 176)
    - The Shepherd School Student Council, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 177)
    - Rice Shooting Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 178)
    - Rice Sketch Comedy, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 179)
    - Rice Collegiate Skydiving Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 180)
    - The Slavic Club of Rice University, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 181)
    - Society for the Advancement of Material and Process Engineering (SAMPE), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 182)
    - Rice Society of Automotive Engineers, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 183)
    - Society of Flamenco Arts at Rice, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 184)
    - The Rice University Chapter of Society of Petroleum Engineers (SPE), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 185)
    - Rice University Chapter of the Society of Physics Students, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 186)
    - The Rice Society for Textile Arts and Beadwork, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Society of Women Engineers, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - The Rice University Solar Car Team, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Rice Solar Decathlon, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - South Asian Society, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Space Physics and Astronomy Club, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - The Speaking Club of Rice University (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Spontaneous Combustion, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Rice Sport Management Club, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Rice Sportsmanship Club (RSC), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Rice Squash Club, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Standard Transmission Driver's Club, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Statistics and Probability Club, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Student Admission Council, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Student Ambassadors, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Student Association of Health Sciences, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Student Committee on Near Eastern Affairs (SCONEA), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Rice Student Health Association, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - The Student Religious Council of the Rice Institute, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Rice Student Volunteer Program (RSVP), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Students for Athletic Spirit & Support (SASS), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Students for a Capitalist Society, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Rice Students for Carter/Mondale, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Students for a Free Tibet, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Students for Global Justice, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Students for Policy Awareness, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Rice Students for Progressive Activism, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Rice University Students for Sensible Drug Policy, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Students' International Meditation Society of Rice University, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Students Organized Against Rape, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Rice Students Seeking Total Tans (RSSTT), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Students' Speakers Forum, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Student Voices, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Rice University Synthetic Biology Club, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Tae Kwon Do, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Tai Chi Association, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - The Rice Taiwanese Association, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Taiwanese Student Association, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - Tau Beta Pi, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Rice Club Tennis Team, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Tetra, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Texas State Student Organization, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Thai Students Association, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - Thoreau College, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - T.R.U.T.H., n.d. (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - Rice Turkish Student Association, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 46)
    - Transfer Student Club, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - Tri Club, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - Rice Ultimate Frisbee Club, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 49)
    - The Rice Undergraduate Academic Review, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 50)
    - Rice Undergraduate Biochemistry Journal Club, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 51)
    - Rice Undergraduate Biological Journal Club, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 52)
    - The Rice Undergraduate History Major Society, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 53)
    - United Campuses to Prevent Nuclear War (UCAM), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 54)
    - United We Stand America, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 55)
    - Unity '08, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 56)
    - The University Blue, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 57)
    - Vegetarian Club, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 58)
    - Victory Campus Ministries, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 59)
    - Rice Water Polo Club, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 60)
    - Web Design and Development, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 61)
    - Weight Training Club, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 62)
    - The Wesley Foundation, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 63)
    - Wharton and Rice Mentoring (WARM), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 64)
    - Will Rice Intellectual and Cultural Enrichment Society, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 65)
    - Wine, Pizza, & Metaphysics Club, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 66)
    - Wine Society, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 67)
    - Woman's Organization for Radical Discussion (WORD), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 68)
    - The Rice Women Alliance, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 69)
    - Women in Agriculture, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 70)
    - The Association for Women's Awareness of the Right to Equality (AWARE), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 71)
    - Rice Women's Club Volleyball, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 72)
    - Rice Women's Fast Pitch Softball Team, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 73)
    - Rice Women's Interest Network, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 74)
    - Rice Women's Lacrosse Club, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 75)
    - Rice Women Rugby Club, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 76)
    - Rice Women's Soccer Club, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 77)
    - Rice Women's Ultimate: Club Constitution, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 78)
    - Rice Women's Water Polo Club, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 79)
    - Wordsworthless Society, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 80)
    - World Peace Buddhist Society, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 81)
    - Wrestling Club, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 82)
    - The Writer's Bloc, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 83)
    - Club Yo: Rice's Organization for Yo-Yo Enthusiasts, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 84)
    - Rice Yoga Club, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 85)
    - The Young Americans for Freedom, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 86)
    - Rice University Young Democrats, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 87)
    - Rice Young Life Fellowship, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 88)
    - Zen Club, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 89)
    - 5H Club, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 90)
    - The 12 Hours Club (12HC), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 91)
  - Sub-Series VII: Publications
    - SA Advertisements, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 92)
    - SA Advertisements, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 93)
    - SA Advertisements, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 94)
    - Advertisements, 2007-2008 (Box 27, Folder 95)
    - Advertisements, 2008-2010 (Box 27, Folder 96)
    - Student Organizations Manual, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 97)
    - The Clubs Manual, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 98)
    - The Clubs Manual, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 99)
    - The Clubs Manual, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 100)
    - Newcomers Guide, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 101)
    - Newcomers Guide, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 102)
    - Newcomers Guide Advertisements, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 103)
    - New Student Mail Out Letters, 1997-2000 (Box 22, Folder 104)
    - New Student Representatives, 2005-2006 (Box 27, Folder 105)
    - New Student Rep Application, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 106)
    - NSR Advertisements, 2008-2009 (Box 27, Folder 107)
  - Sub-Series IX: Agendas
    - Minutes and Agendas, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 108)
    - Meeting Agendas, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 109)
    - Agendas, 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 110)
    - Agendas, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 111)
    - Agendas, 2000-2001 (Box 27, Folder 112)
    - Agendas, 2001-2002 (Box 27, Folder 113)
    - Meeting Minutes, 2002-2003 (Box 27, Folder 114)
    - Agendas, 2004-2006 (Box 27, Folder 115)
    - Meeting Minutes, 2005-2006 (Box 27, Folder 116)
    - Agendas, 2007-2008 (Box 27, Folder 117)
  - Sub-Series X: Projects
    - Athletics Survey, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Institutional Memory Database, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Organizations Membership, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Willy Week Jacks, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Projects, 1988-1989 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - MANA Major Review, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Projects, 1990-1991 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Projects, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Intramural Sports Research, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - High-Speed Rail, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Youth Task Force Against Crime, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Projects, 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Projects, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Projects, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - RMC & Rec Center Study, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Universal Card, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Projects, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Task Force on Admission Materials, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - U.S. News Ranking, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Green Lights Program, 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Projects, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Blanket Tax, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Projects, 1998-1999 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Dialogue on Race, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - N.O.D., 1999 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Solutions Conference, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Projects, 1999-2000 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Construction, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Martel College Founding, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Projects, 2000-2001 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - College Cheer Reform, 2000-2001 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Web Steering Committee, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Rice Associates Dinner, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Cheers Forum, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Projects, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Honor Code Research, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Meal Plan, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Old Wiess Field Proposal, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Projects, 2002-2003 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - EMS Funding, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Exam Proctoring, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - Honor Code, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - LPAP, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - Silver Card, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - Sports Survey, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - Summer Storage, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 46)
    - Health Survey, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 47)
    - Hedge Hopper, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 48)
    - SA Issues, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 49)
    - Projects, 2005-2006 (Box 28, Folder 50)
    - Call to Conversation, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Hedge Hopper, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Projects, 2006-2007 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Hedge Hopper Program, 2006-2007 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - SA Projects, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Commencement Speaker, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Goals, 2007-2008 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Space Reallocation, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Study Breaks, 2009-2011 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Coffee House, 2010-2012 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Asset Liquidation Funds Appropriations, 2011 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Concerts, 2011 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Willy Week, 2012 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Bike Sharing Program, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series XI: SA President Papers
    - Barry Nicholson: President Papers, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Tom Perrault: Presidents Folder, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Adam E. Carr Secretary Papers, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Andy Karsner Presidents Papers, 1988-1989 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Dennis Abbott: Secretary Papers, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Mitra Miller Treasurer Papers, 1990-1991 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Rachel Levitt: Secretary Papers, 1990-1991 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Celeste Campbell Secretary Papers, 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Mitra Miller: Presidents Folder, 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - John Shield's President Papers, 1992-1993 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Patrick Good's Secretary Papers, 1992-1993 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Christine Yeh Secretary Papers, 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Carrie Smith Secretary Papers, 1997-1998 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Anne Countiss: President Papers, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Caroline Glendenning Secretary Papers, 2001-2002 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Director of Technology files (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Senate Transfer Disc files (Box 29, Folder 30)
- Series XVI: Google Drive, 2009-2019
  - Sub-Series A: Blanket Tax
    - 2009-2010
      Scope and Contents
      Files containing information on blanket taxes, Hedgehopper, election guidelines, logos, legislation, club constitutions, and university standing committee minutes.
    - 2013-2014
    - 2014-2015
      Conditions Governing Access
      SA content - 2018/2019 SA President Ariana Engles requested a blanket 5 year restriction after the point of creation.
    - 2015-2016
    - 2016-2017
    - 2017-2018
    - 2018-2019
    - Initiative fund and transition document, 2015-2016
  - General election guidelines, 2016
  - Hedgehopper, 2015-2019
  - Sub-Series B: Legislation, 2009-2019
    - 2009-2010
    - 2010-2011
    - 2011-2012
    - 2012-2013
    - 2013-2014
    - 2014-2015
    - 2015-2016
    - 2016-2017
    - 2017-2018
    - 2018-2019
  - Logos, 2015-2017
  - Sub-Series C: President's historical items, 2012-2019
    - Executive Cabinet meeting minutes, 2014
    - Historical, 2011-2013
    - SA Meetings, 2014-2015
    - SA40k, 2014
    - President's info, 2014-2019
  - Sub-Series D: SA club constitutions, 2014-2017
    - 2014-2015
    - 2015-2016
    - 2016-2017
  - Sub-Series E: SA files by term, 2009-2019
    - President's historical items, 2012-2019
    - 2009-2010
      PDF files contain information documenting the 2009-2010 Student Association term.
    - 2010-2011
      PDF and jpeg files contain information documenting the 2010-2011 Student Association term.
    - 2011-2012
      PDF files contain information documenting the 2011-2012 Student Association term.
    - 2012-2013
      PDF files contain information documenting the 2012-2013 and 2013-2014 Student Association term.
    - 2013-2014
    - 2014-2015
      PDF, JPEG, MP4, and PNG files contain information documenting the 2014-2015 Student Association term.
    - 2015-2016
      PDF, JPEG, HTML, PNG, and MP4 files contain information documenting the 2015-2016 Student Association term.
    - 2016-2017
      PDF, JPEG, HTML, and PNG files contain information documenting the 2016-2017 Student Association term.
    - 2017-2018
      PDF, JPEG, PNG, HTML, and MP4 files contain information documenting the 2017-2018 Student Association term.
    - 2018-2019
      PDF, GIF, HTML, JPG, MP4, M4A, and M4V files contain information documenting the 2018-2019 Student Association term.
  - University standing committee meeting minutes, 2017-2018
- Series XVII: Addenda 2020
  - Rice Student Volunteer Program (RSVP), 1986-2000
    - The National Creative Education Partnership Award Plaque, 1990-02-26 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Opportunities Listings, 1986-1989 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Photographs of Trips and Activities (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Sub-Series A: Photographs of Volunteering Activities, 1996-1999 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Beach Cleanup, 1996
      - Unlabeled, ca. 1996
      - Adventure Play, 1997
      - Friends of Hermann Park: The Wetlands, 1997
      - Habitat for Humanity, 1997
      - Houston Humane Society, 1997